us-elitegear.com 2010-12-11

# US Elite Gear: Finest Quality Tactical Gear for the Armed and First Responder professionals.

| 

| 

> ## Privacy Policy
> 
> **What information do we collect?**
> 
> You may visit our site anonymously.  However, when ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and / or credit card information. 
> 
> **What do we use your information for?**
> 
> The information we collect from you may be used: 
> 
>   * To personalize your experience  \- your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs
>   * To improve our website \- we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you
>   * To improve customer service \- your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs 
>   * To process transactions
>   * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 
>   * To send periodic emails 
> 

> 
> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 
> 
> The email address you provide for order processing will only be used  to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. You must decide to opt-in to our mailing list in order to receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
> 
> _Note:_ If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
> 
> **How do we protect your information?**
> 
> We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. 
> 
> We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.  Security certificates are issued by Thawte, a leading data encryption company. 
> 
> Our ecommerce software complies with the Payment Card Industry (PCI) Data Security Standard.  PCI is an agreed upon standard by all of the major credit card companies.  Further, our shopping cart is scanned daily by McAfee Corporation. The network is tested and certified to pass the "McAfee Secure" Security Scan. To help address concerns about possible hacker access to confidential data, the "live" McAfee Secure mark appears in the shopping cart application.
> 
> After a transaction, your private information will not be stored on our servers.
> 
> **Do we use cookies?**
> 
> Yes.  Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
> 
> We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, to enhance your shopping experience.
> 
> **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**
> 
> We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
> 
> **Third party links**
> 
> Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
> 
> **Other**
> 
> By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.  If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.  If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at [customerservice@us-elitegear.com](mailto:customerservice@us-elitegear.com). 

|   
---|---|---
